Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/irmas-1b90a894 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Vendor Management Leadership Management

Languages

Spanish (Professional Working)

Certifications

Project Management Professional (PMP)®

Project Management Professional (PMP)

CyberArk Endpoint Privilege Manager (EPM) Certified Pre-Sales Engineer

CompTIA Security+ ce Certification AWS Certified Solutions Architect –

Associate

Irma S.

Identity Access Management - Cybersecurity St Petersburg, Florida, United States

Summary

Experienced. Knowledgeable. An Army veteran. A "Unicorn". These are some of the words that describe Irma Shattuck. Hello! I am a Senior IT Technical Program Manager in Cybersecurity, Identity and Access Management, Privileged Access Management, Healthcare, IT General Controls Auditing, AWS, Biometric Science, Clinical Trials, Retail, and Shared App Services. I am a former CIO with the State of Tennessee's Department of Education. While there, I successfully penned, along with Microsoft and the CBER (Center for Business and Economic Research) of the University of Tennessee, a government grant in the amount of \$500M to establish a statewide Student Longitudinal Database. I have continued to build upon this success by expanding my knowledge through education and certifications in the fields previously mentioned. This includes the PMP (Project Management Professional Certificate), CompTIA Security + Certification, and many more. I would excitedly bring this leadership, team building, and mentoring skills, the wealth of knowledge, and experience to support the company's goals and visions, successful customer experience, and build on continued success.

Experience

Integral Partners LLC
Manager, Privileged Access Management/CyberArk Business
Development Lead
January 2023 - Present (4 months)
Boulder, Colorado, United States

Experfy

Senior Consultant Identity and Access Management - Cybersecurity July 2022 - Present (10 months)

Greater Tampa Bay Area

Implement technological cybersecurity IAM (Identity and Access Management) solutions to solve business problems by analyzing IT systems and

infrastructure, and diagnosing IT system problems, inefficiencies, and weaknesses. Analyze and determine security threats, implement a technological solution for business needs and best practices and collaborate with technical in-house teams for familiarity with technology. Train IT teams, on new solutions and monitor the success of IT solutions.

lululemon

Senior Security Engineer/Senior Technical Program Manager IAM February 2022 - October 2022 (9 months)

Greater Seattle Area

Manager for implementation/support engineers and developers. Led research and development for optimizing and streamlining implemented identity management solutions and implementing customized identity management solutions via SailPoint IIQ 8.2, Delinea (formerly Thycotic), and Britiv Platforms.

Managed migration of SailPoint IDN to SailPoint IIQ 7.2 and brand new Green Platform of IIQ 8.2.

Evaluate and streamline architecture, design, planning, customization, configuration, and implementation for SailPoint IIQ 8.2

Designed and implemented connectors for ServiceNow, Workday, Active Directory, LDAPS, and Oracle plus custom connectors for legacy/on-premise applications.

Develop custom rules, workflow configuration, development, and third-party system integration.

Responsible for vulnerability detection using Endpoint Security for Preexecution and runtime machine learning, detection of malware and ransomware threats. Responsible for solving false positives and protection against scripts, memory, and browser attacks with a high focus on crown jewel assets.

CNH Industrial

Senior IAM-PAM Engineer, Cyber Defense & Engineering October 2021 - February 2022 (5 months)

Racine, Wisconsin, United States

As a Divestiture from Fiat, Italy, I was responsible for leading and managing a new PAM implementation for CNHi's spinoff by moving accounts from CyberArk Privileged Access Management (PAM) security system to a brand new platform on Thycotic (Delinea) for over 66,000 users that boosted security by 85%

Implemented Endpoint Security to detect and eliminate risk exposure to critical platforms and physical and virtual devices with SOC monitoring and remediation

Create a procedure manual containing Standard Operation Procedures to improve the performance of security infrastructure, thus boosting efficiency by 70%

Coached 22 team members on the best practices to create effective IAM/PAM solutions

Collaborated with other management officials to define the architecture and devise new tactics to maintain security infrastructure for optimal performance

IQVIA

Senior Consultant, Information Security IAM/PAM April 2021 - October 2021 (7 months)

North Carolina, United States

Managed 4 global security projects, CyberArk, Thycotic, CrowdStrike, SilverFort, and SailPoint IDN initiating innovative solutions that drove production to completion

Managed Proof of Value for CyberArk, Thycotic for PAM and SilverFort, and CrowdStrike for endpoint security detections and monitoring

Led project meetings and stakeholder meetings weekly and daily, creating an open and positive environment in which critical ideas were exchanged Oversaw implementation of PAM platforms for Active Directory and LDAP as well as applications to Azure AD and AWS platforms that increased security by15%

Responsible for the IGA integration of SailPoint IDN and CyberArk for employee life-cycle management

Cultivated workflows of cross-functional teams to achieve better organization and cost savings of 150K

PricewaterhouseCoopers Advisory, Capital Projects & Infrastructure CyberArk Global Technical Program Manager, Security Engineer October 2019 - April 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Global Senior Technical Program Manager responsible for the role out of CyberArk Privilege Account Management for 149 Countries
Responsible for the integration and CyberArk and the Enterprise SailPoint installation for IGA for the management of risks, compliance issues, employee life cycle management and least privilege access decisions in a SaaS platform.

Managed PAM Engineers, developers, project managers, and project coordinators

Controlled a \$6.8 million budget that included employee/contractor employee management, purchase of new infrastructure devices, and technical refresh devices

Devised Break-glass procedures for legacy applications, and was responsible for infrastructure refresh

Amgen

Senior Security Engineer Cyber Resilience, Senior Program Manager September 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Investigated and successfully implemented the company's ability to protect and isolate all

manufacturing sites from cyber-attacks and sustaining operations after an enterprise cyber-attack via strategic network segmentation, endpoint connectivity, and security controls.

Implemented Multi-factor Authentication(MFA) and Single Sign-On (SSO) procedures implementing

SAML 1.1 and SAML 2.0 protocols, OAuth, and OpenID

Community Health Systems

Senior Security Engineer Technical Program Manager IAM/PAM November 2016 - January 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Franklin, Tennessee, United States

Governed the Identity and Access Management (IAM) for EMR/EHR applications across 202 facilities, emphasizing operational excellence for migration from the McKesson EHR platform to the Cerner platform Implemented Single Sign On (SSO), Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA), Rolebased access controls (RBAC), and least privilege for all hospital staff and vendor management

Monitored risks and threats to the system via endpoint security, and devised viable solutions with team members to better secure all software applications, and critical network devices thus accomplishing a 25% rise in security

Cigna-HealthSpring

Director Data Governance and Risk Compliance, Information Management

March 2012 - March 2016 (4 years 1 month)

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Spearheaded Information Security Sarbanes Oxley Compliance program practices

Collaborator for stakeholders and application owners for data governance and compliance according to NIST, CMS ISACA, OWASP, SABSA, and company data governance, risks, and compliance practices.

Managed a team of 185 on-shore ad off-shore resources, a resource manager, and 16 embedded Enterprise Senior Project Managers

HOSPITAL CORPORATIONS OF AMERICA (HCA)

Senior Project Management Consultant PMO June 2011 - February 2012 (9 months)

Greater Nashville Area, TN

- Spearheaded \$10M ISAS (Integrated System and Scheduling) Project
- Coordinated with Information Technology Stakeholders and Parallon Business Stakeholders
- · Liaison for Meditech and McKesson Stakeholders
- Supervised team of 12 on-shore and offshore System Engineers and Business Analysts
- Streamlined project deliverables to maximize team strategy into efficient alignment with core business priorities.
- Met with Executive Leadership Team on a weekly basis for project status updates

Bridgestone North America Senior Project Manager - PMO September 2010 - May 2011 (9 months)

Greater Nashville Area, TN

- SAP Technical Interface Director for the implementation of the global OTC (Order to Cash) project.
- Project liaison between the company and the geographical regions of Asia,
 South America and the United States
- Successfully identified and coordinated readiness of all system environments to include legacy systems.
- Directed code migration and systems environment integration for all new systems and legacy systems.
- Lead change management processes
- Supervised the installation and use of middleware traffic monitor Web sphere software solution.
- Organized the integration of old platforms for Websphere utilization.

 Project included over 150 new systems and approximately 120 legacy systems.

State of Tennessee
Chief Analytic Officer/CIO
October 2008 - September 2010 (2 years)
Greater Nashville Area, TN

- Implemented the K-12 Data Warehouse and Business Intelligence (BI) initiatives with a strong focus on driving technical and architectural solutions and discussions to support the inter-departmental agencies business needs and requirements.
- Spearheaded the team collaboration between project stakeholders consisting
 of Microsoft, CBER (University of Tennessee Center for Business and
 Economic Research), and United States Department of Justice, United States
 of the Department of Education and the United States Department Education
 American and Reinvestment Act of 2009.
- Implemented Data Government, Risks and Compliance for Department of Education Data ecosystem.
- The State of Tennessee Department of Education was awarded Stimulus Funds in the amount of \$500,000,000.
- Successfully leveraged the State of Tennessee, Department of Education data assets to exceed the Agencies business goals.
- Assumed increased responsibility for writing Grants and applying for Stimulus
 Funds to support the Agencies goals and strategic directions.

Education

University of America

Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.), Organizational Leadership · (2013 - 2015)

University of Phoenix

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology and Telecommunication · (2011 - 2014)

University of America

Master's Degree, Organizational Leadership · (2011 - 2013)

University of America

Bachelor's Degree, Leadership · (2009 - 2010)

University of Phoenix
Associate's Degree, Business Administration and Management,
General · (2007 - 2009)